Finding aid for the Paul Monash Papers LSC.2312
UCLA Library Special Collections
Paul Monash papers
1956-1969
UCLA Library Special Collections
Monash, Paul
LSC.2312
150 Linear Feet (320 boxes)
Paul Monash was a writer and producer and served as a producer for the television shows Peyton Place and Judd, for the Defense among many others. He also produced motion pictures, such as Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid and Slaughterhouse-five. The collection consists of first and final draft scripts and writer's notes for the television series Peyton Place and Judd, for the Defense.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Paul Monash, 1969.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9980429643606533
Biography/History
Paul Monash was born in Harlem, NY on June 14, 1917. He earned a B.A. in journalism from the University of Wisconsin and an M.A. in education from Columbia University. He started his career in early television contributing scripts to Studio One, Playhouse 90, and Kraft Theater. In 1959 Monash produced, and wrote the pilot show for series The Untouchables. He went on to Twentieth Century-Fox writing the pilot episode and serving as producer for series Peyton Place and serving as producer for Judd for the Defense. His film credits include Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid, Slaughterhouse-Five, and Carrie among others. He won a Golden Globe Award (1980) for the television film All Quiet on the Western Front, Humanitas Award (1997), for George Wallace, and 2000, he received the Paddy Chayefsky Laurel Award from the Writers Guild of America. Paul Monash died in January 2003.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of writer and producer, Paul Monash. Included are first and final draft scripts and writer's notes for the television series Judd for the Defense and Peyton Place.
Organization and Arrangement
The collections is arranged in loose chronological order by television series title.
Television writers -- United States.; Television producers and directors -- United States; Monash, Paul
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May-December 1965, May-September 1966 (Box 6)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE August, November-December 1966 (Box 10)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November 1966 (Box 26)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE October-November 1966 (Box 29)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1966 (Box 33)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1966-1967 (Box 30)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE January-May 1966, November-December 1967 (Box 5)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May-July 1967 (Box 7)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November-December 1966, March-September 1968 (Box 8)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE September 1966, December 1967, February 1968 (Box 3)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November 1966, June-October 1967 (Box 39)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE February, May-June, September 1967 (Box 10)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May-June 1967 (Box 11)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May-September 1967 (Box 16)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May, July-October 1967 (Box 23)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE August-September, December 1967 (Box 24)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November-December 1967 (Box 34)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE June, July, September 1967 (Box 135)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE September-October 1967 (Box 270)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November 1967, August 1968 (Box 1)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE July 1967, July, October-November 1968 (Box 2)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE July-August 1967, April-May, July 1968 (Box 4)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November-December 1967, January, March-December 1968 (Box 8)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE January-December 1967, January-December 1968 (Box 12)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE April-May, July-December 1967, January 1968 (Box 13)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE September-October 1967, June, August 1968 (Box 17)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1967-1968 (Box 19)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May-June 1967, December 1968 (Box 25)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE November-December 1967, 1968 (Box 35)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE June, August, October-December 1967, January 1968 (Box 37)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE December 1967, January, April 1968 (Box 38)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE October-December 1968 (Box 5)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE August-October 1968 (Box 6)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE March-June 1968 (Box 9)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE July-September, November 1968 (Box 14)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE August-October 1968 (Box 15)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE July-August, October, December 1968 (Box 18)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1968 (Box 20)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1968 (Box 21)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE April-May, July-August 1968 (Box 22)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1968 (Box 27)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE June-September 1968 (Box 28)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE May-July, December 1968 (Box 31)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE October-December 1968 (Box 36)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE 1968, 1969 (Box 32)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE December 1969 (Box 8)
- JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE January 1969 (Box 12)
- PEYTON PLACE (Box 146)
- PEYTON PLACE (Box 169)
- PEYTON PLACE (Box 308)
- PEYTON PLACE 1956, 1958-1959, 1962-1966 (Box 104)
- PEYTON PLACE May 1957, January 1967 (Box 152)
- PEYTON PLACE August 1962, April-June, August 1963 (Box 144)
- PEYTON PLACE November 1962, 1967-1968 (Box 153)
- PEYTON PLACE June-July, September, November 1963 (Box 53)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1963 (Box 151)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1963, July-August 1964 (Box 194)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1983, April-June 1964, July 1966 (Box 260)
- PEYTON PLACE 1963-1964, September-October 1968 (Box 132)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1963, March-April 1966 (Box 267)
- PEYTON PLACE 1963-1966 (Box 293)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June, August-September 1963, November 1967 (Box 266)
- PEYTON PLACE 1963-1968 (Box 214)
- PEYTON PLACE August, October 1964 (Box 123)
- PEYTON PLACE January-March 1964 (Box 128)
- PEYTON PLACE April-June 1964 (Box 246)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1964 (Box 250)
- PEYTON PLACE February-March, June-July 1964 (Box 270)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April, June-July 1964 (Box 291)
- PEYTON PLACE September 1964 (Box 292)
- PEYTON PLACE January, July, September 1964, April 1965 (Box 53)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1964, February, April-May, November 1965 (Box 84)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1965 (Box 87)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1964, June, August-September 1965 (Box 99)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1964, February 1965 (Box 113)
- PEYTON PLACE September, December 1964, October 1965 (Box 165)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1964, April, July, September 1965 (Box 176)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1964, January 1965 (Box 180)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1964, January 1965 (Box 200)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1964, January-February 1965 (Box 202)
- PEYTON PLACE October 1964, November-December 1965 (Box 203)
- PEYTON PLACE July, November 1964, April 1965 (Box 223)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1964, February-March 1965 (Box 241)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1964, July, September, December 1965 (Box 244)
- PEYTON PLACE July-September 1964, January-March 1965 (Box 247)
- PEYTON PLACE April-November 1964, June-July 1965 (Box 268)
- PEYTON PLACE September 1964, September 1965 (Box 287)
- PEYTON PLACE June, July 1964, September 1965 (Box 312)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1964, March, July 1965, January 1966 (Box 51)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1964, January 1965, March-May 1966 (Box 183)
- PEYTON PLACE October 1964, 1965, February 1966 (Box 206)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1964, January 1965, February-March 1966 (Box 235)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1964, January 1965, April 1968 (Box 232)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1966 (Box 52)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1966 (Box 110)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1964, August, October 1966 (Box 158)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1966 (Box 182)
- PEYTON PLACE July-September 1964, May 1966 (Box 225)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1964, February 1966 (Box 251)
- PEYTON PLACE August 1964, May-July 1966 (Box 253)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1964, June, August 1966 (Box 279)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1964, May-June 1966 (Box 280)
- PEYTON PLACE April, July 1964, September 1966, December 1967 (Box 102)
- PEYTON PLACE September 1964, September-October 1966, May 1967 (Box 114)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1964, May 1966, March 1967 (Box 145)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964, November 1966, March 1967 (Box 161)
- PEYTON PLACE June-July 1964, December 1966, January 1967 (Box 234)
- PEYTON PLACE August-December 1964, July-August 1967 (Box 134)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1964, January, April 1967 (Box 138)
- PEYTON PLACE September 1964, June-July 1967 (Box 175)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1964, June-July, September 1967 (Box 230)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1967, January-April 1967, May 1968 (Box 93)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1964, January 1967, May 1968 (Box 107)
- PEYTON PLACE September 1964, January, November 1967, June 1968 (Box 208)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1968 (Box 126)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964, 1968 (Box 130)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1968 (Box 163)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1968 (Box 257)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1968 (Box 258)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1968 (Box 259)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1969 (Box 101)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1969 (Box 106)
- PEYTON PLACE 1964-1969 (Box 109)
- PEYTON PLACE May, October 1964, January 1969 (Box 187)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1965 (Box 40)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April, October-November 1965 (Box 42)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February, May 1965 (Box 47)
- PEYTON PLACE February-April 1965 (Box 57)
- PEYTON PLACE March, June, September 1965 (Box 90)
- PEYTON PLACE June, August, October-November 1965 (Box 98)
- PEYTON PLACE June, August, October-November 1965 (Box 100)
- PEYTON PLACE September-November 1965 (Box 117)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February, April 1965 (Box 139)
- PEYTON PLACE February, May 1965 (Box 147)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February 1965 (Box 173)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1965 (Box 174)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1965 (Box 181)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April 1965 (Box 189)
- PEYTON PLACE March-May 1965 (Box 190)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1965 (Box 194)
- PEYTON PLACE April 1965 (Box 196)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1965 (Box 197)
- PEYTON PLACE June-July 1965 (Box 198)
- PEYTON PLACE August-October 1965 (Box 199)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1965 (Box 219)
- PEYTON PLACE April, June-July, December 1965 (Box 238)
- PEYTON PLACE January, March, June, December 1965 (Box 243)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May, November-December 1965 (Box 248)
- PEYTON PLACE June-September 1965 (Box 261)
- PEYTON PLACE February-April, August-October 1965 (Box 274)
- PEYTON PLACE February-March, May-June, September-November 1965 (Box 284)
- PEYTON PLACE June-August 1965 (Box 296)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965 (Box 300)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965 (Box 301)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965 (Box 302)
- PEYTON PLACE June, July 1965 (Box 307)
- PEYTON PLACE April, October 1965, April 1966 (Box 60)
- PEYTON PLACE September 1965, July 1966 (Box 72)
- PEYTON PLACE January, October 1965, January, July-September 1968 (Box 75)
- PEYTON PLACE May, September 1965, January 1966 (Box 88)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1965, 1966 (Box 91)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1965, January-February 1966 (Box 105)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1965, January 1966 (Box 111)
- PEYTON PLACE February, April, November 1965, March-May 1966 (Box 133)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1966 (Box 141)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1965, April-July 1966 (Box 143)
- PEYTON PLACE January, September-October 1965, March, July 1966 (Box 155)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April 1965, August-September 1966 (Box 157)
- PEYTON PLACE April 1965, January, September 1966 (Box 191)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February, August-October 1965, November 1966 (Box 201)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1965, February-April 1966 (Box 204)
- PEYTON PLACE May, August 1965, March, July 1966 (Box 220)
- PEYTON PLACE February 1965, March-June 1966 (Box 226)
- PEYTON PLACE August 1965, February-March 1966 (Box 233)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1965, March-April 1966 (Box 249)
- PEYTON PLACE January, November-December 1965, January-December 1966 (Box 262)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1965, January-February, April 1966 (Box 271)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October, December 1965, January-February 1966 (Box 272)
- PEYTON PLACE November 1965, April-June 1966 (Box 275)
- PEYTON PLACE May, December 1965, January, November 1966 (Box 277)
- PEYTON PLACE March, October-November 1965, February-March 1966 (Box 278)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1965, September-October 1966 (Box 281)
- PEYTON PLACE October, December 1965, January-March, November 1966 (Box 286)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1965, March 1966 (Box 289)
- PEYTON PLACE May-September, November 1965, March 1966 (Box 304)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1965, September 1966, January 1967 (Box 71)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1966, June-August 1967 (Box 83)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1965, January 1966, November 1967 (Box 252)
- PEYTON PLACE October 1965, January 1966, November 1967 (Box 264)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1965, May-June 1967 (Box 94)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1967 (Box 97)
- PEYTON PLACE August, October, December 1965, January 1967 (Box 127)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1965, January, August-September 1967 (Box 176)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1965, January, May, November 1967 (Box 215)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1967 (Box 228)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1965, April-May 1967 (Box 288)
- PEYTON PLACE February-April 1965, May 1967 (Box 294)
- PEYTON PLACE June-September 1965, November-December 1967 (Box 305)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1965, November 1967, January 1968 (Box 73)
- PEYTON PLACE May 1965, August 1967, January-February 1968 (Box 221)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1968 (Box 54)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965, September, October 1968 (Box 81)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1965, November 1968 (Box 96)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1965, August 1968 (Box 118)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1965, August 1968 (Box 119)
- PEYTON PLACE July, September 1965, March-April 1968 (Box 122)
- PEYTON PLACE June-December 1965, August, December 1968 (Box 142)
- PEYTON PLACE June, September 1965, October-December 1968 (Box 156)
- PEYTON PLACE February-April 1965, May, July 1968 (Box 185)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1965, September-October 1968 (Box 265)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1969 (Box 51)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1969 (Box 69)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1969 (Box 108)
- PEYTON PLACE 1965-1969 (Box 131)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1965, May-June 1969 (Box 149)
- PEYTON PLACE May 1965, January 1969 (Box 256)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966 (Box 46)
- PEYTON PLACE August-October 1966 (Box 56)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966 (Box 79)
- PEYTON PLACE May-July 1966 (Box 116)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June, October-November 1966 (Box 121)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September, November-December 1966 (Box 135)
- PEYTON PLACE June-July, November-December 1966 (Box 156)
- PEYTON PLACE August-October 1966 (Box 166)
- PEYTON PLACE April 1966 (Box 168)
- PEYTON PLACE September, October 1966 (Box 170)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1966 (Box 171)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1966 (Box 172)
- PEYTON PLACE April-June 1966 (Box 177)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1966 (Box 178)
- PEYTON PLACE May, July-August 1966 (Box 184)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966 (Box 211)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966 (Box 213)
- PEYTON PLACE June-August 1966 (Box 217)
- PEYTON PLACE January, February, April, June-July 1966 (Box 221)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1966 (Box 229)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June, October-November 1966 (Box 231)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1966 (Box 237)
- PEYTON PLACE March-May 1966 (Box 238)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1966 (Box 240)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April 1966 (Box 241)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1966 (Box 247)
- PEYTON PLACE January, March 1966 (Box 284)
- PEYTON PLACE June-July 1966 (Box 287)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May, October-November 1966 (Box 290)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966 (Box 314)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1966, March, May 1966 (Box 313)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1966, June-July 1967 (Box 63)
- PEYTON PLACE October 1966, May-June 1967 (Box 67)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1966, March, July-August 1967 (Box 70)
- PEYTON PLACE March-May 1966, June, August-September 1967 (Box 92)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1966, April-May 1967 (Box 154)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1966, May-June 1967 (Box 179)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April, June 1966, June, December 1967 (Box 187)
- PEYTON PLACE July-November 1966, March-April 1967 (Box 212)
- PEYTON PLACE September-December 1966, January-April 1967 (Box 216)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1966, January 1967 (Box 239)
- PEYTON PLACE May 1966, December 1967 (Box 261)
- PEYTON PLACE September, December 1966, January-February 1967 (Box 279)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1966, January, March-April 1967 (Box 282)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1966, June-July 1967 (Box 299)
- PEYTON PLACE February-April, October 1966, May 1967 (Box 320)
- PEYTON PLACE May-August 1966, 1967, July-October 1968 (Box 58)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966, June, August 1967, April 1968 (Box 311)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1966, September-October 1968 (Box 41)
- PEYTON PLACE May 1966, April-October 1968 (Box 55)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966-1968 (Box 66)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966-1968 (Box 188)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1966, May 1968 (Box 242)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April, June 1966, March 1968 (Box 243)
- PEYTON PLACE June-August 1966, January-February 1968 (Box 245)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966-1968 (Box 269)
- PEYTON PLACE 1966-1968 (Box 269)
- PEYTON PLACE February 1966, February, June 1968 (Box 310)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1967 (Box 43)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1967 (Box 43)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1967 (Box 44)
- PEYTON PLACE August-October 1967 (Box 49)
- PEYTON PLACE September-November 1967 (Box 65)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1967 (Box 67)
- PEYTON PLACE September-November 1967 (Box 76)
- PEYTON PLACE April-August 1967 (Box 78)
- PEYTON PLACE April 1967 (Box 80)
- PEYTON PLACE November 1967 (Box 92)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June, August-September 1967 (Box 128)
- PEYTON PLACE April, June 1967 (Box 136)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1967 (Box 137)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1967 (Box 150)
- PEYTON PLACE February-March, July-August 1967 (Box 156)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1967 (Box 160)
- PEYTON PLACE January, May-July, September 1967 (Box 191)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May, July 1967 (Box 192)
- PEYTON PLACE April, July 1967 (Box 201)
- PEYTON PLACE June-August 1967 (Box 207)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1967 (Box 218)
- PEYTON PLACE February-March, May 1967 (Box 222)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1967 (Box 254)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1967 (Box 267)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1967 (Box 276)
- PEYTON PLACE April-June 1967 (Box 279)
- PEYTON PLACE May-July 1967 (Box 285)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1967 (Box 288)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1967 (Box 317)
- PEYTON PLACE 1967-1968 (Box 50)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August 1967, July, December 1968 (Box 74)
- PEYTON PLACE January, October 1967, February, December 1968 (Box 74)
- PEYTON PLACE June, August 1967, May, December 1968 (Box 75)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August, October 1967, February, December 1968 (Box 77)
- PEYTON PLACE April-June 1967, June 1968 (Box 84)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1967, July-August 1968 (Box 89)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February, April 1967, June-July 1968 (Box 90)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1967, January 1968 (Box 125)
- PEYTON PLACE March, May, July 1967, February 1968 (Box 140)
- PEYTON PLACE June, August 1967, January 1968 (Box 165)
- PEYTON PLACE January, April-May 1967, June 1968 (Box 205)
- PEYTON PLACE June, November 1967, July-October 1968 (Box 220)
- PEYTON PLACE June 1967, April-May 1968 (Box 263)
- PEYTON PLACE January 1967, January, May-July, October 1968 (Box 277)
- PEYTON PLACE March, September 1967, January, December 1968 (Box 278)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1967, May-June 1968 (Box 281)
- PEYTON PLACE April, July 1967, May-June, November 1968 (Box 304)
- PEYTON PLACE February-March, June 1968 (Box 48)
- PEYTON PLACE January, April, June 1968 (Box 59)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September 1968 (Box 61)
- PEYTON PLACE January, March, September-November 1968 (Box 64)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August, December 1968 (Box 68)
- PEYTON PLACE 1968 (Box 71)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April, June 1968 (Box 82)
- PEYTON PLACE March-May 1968 (Box 85)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1968 (Box 86)
- PEYTON PLACE August, October-November 1968 (Box 88)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1968 (Box 90)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1968 (Box 95)
- PEYTON PLACE January, March 1968 (Box 102)
- PEYTON PLACE February-April, June, August 1968 (Box 112)
- PEYTON PLACE February 1968 (Box 114)
- PEYTON PLACE October-November 1968 (Box 115)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1968 (Box 120)
- PEYTON PLACE September-December 1968 (Box 124)
- PEYTON PLACE March, May-June 1968 (Box 127)
- PEYTON PLACE January, November-December 1968 (Box 128)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February, September-October 1968 (Box 129)
- PEYTON PLACE November 1968 (Box 154)
- PEYTON PLACE January-February, September-October 1968 (Box 160)
- PEYTON PLACE May 1968 (Box 162)
- PEYTON PLACE February-May 1968 (Box 164)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1968 (Box 167)
- PEYTON PLACE July 1968 (Box 167)
- PEYTON PLACE January-March 1968 (Box 175)
- PEYTON PLACE January-March, August 1968 (Box 176)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June, August-September 1968 (Box 186)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1968 (Box 187)
- PEYTON PLACE November-December 1968 (Box 191)
- PEYTON PLACE April 1968 (Box 193)
- PEYTON PLACE March-April 1968 (Box 195)
- PEYTON PLACE January, July, December 1968 (Box 209)
- PEYTON PLACE January, July, December 1968 (Box 210)
- PEYTON PLACE June, August 1968 (Box 221)
- PEYTON PLACE September-November 1968 (Box 224)
- PEYTON PLACE January, May 1968 (Box 226)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August, November-December 1968 (Box 227)
- PEYTON PLACE September-October 1968 (Box 235)
- PEYTON PLACE June-August 1968 (Box 251)
- PEYTON PLACE May-August, November 1968 (Box 252)
- PEYTON PLACE April, August-October 1968 (Box 255)
- PEYTON PLACE August-September, December 1968 (Box 261)
- PEYTON PLACE January 1968 (Box 264)
- PEYTON PLACE January 1968 (Box 266)
- PEYTON PLACE May, July 1968 (Box 273)
- PEYTON PLACE April-July, September 1968 (Box 283)
- PEYTON PLACE May, December 1968 (Box 290)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1968 (Box 295)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August, October 1968 (Box 297)
- PEYTON PLACE July-September 1968 (Box 298)
- PEYTON PLACE April, August 1968 (Box 303)
- PEYTON PLACE January, November-December 1968 (Box 305)
- PEYTON PLACE April, September 1968 (Box 306)
- PEYTON PLACE February, April 1968 (Box 309)
- PEYTON PLACE February, April-May 1968 (Box 316)
- PEYTON PLACE March 1968 (Box 318)
- PEYTON PLACE April-May 1968 (Box 319)
- PEYTON PLACE July-August, December 1968 (Box 320)
- PEYTON PLACE February 1968, 1963-1966 (Box 62)
- PEYTON PLACE January, March-June, August 1968, January 1969 (Box 72)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1968, January 1969 (Box 103)
- PEYTON PLACE January, July, October-November 1968, May 1969 (Box 147)
- PEYTON PLACE January, March, December 1968, June 1969 (Box 148)
- PEYTON PLACE May-September 1968, January, February 1969 (Box 159)
- PEYTON PLACE January 1968, April 1969 (Box 215)
- PEYTON PLACE October-December 1968, January, March 1969 (Box 236)
- PEYTON PLACE 1968-1969 (Box 262)
- PEYTON PLACE December 1968, January 1969 (Box 277)
- PEYTON PLACE November 1968, January 1969 (Box 311)
- PEYTON PLACE August, September 1968, January 1969 (Box 315)
- PEYTON PLACE January 1969 (Box 77)
- PEYTON PLACE May-June 1969 (Box 96)
- PEYTON PLACE January 1969 (Box 140)
- PEYTON PLACE February-June 1969 (Box 205)